Right, let's take a quick look at what
our Melodía is. Here's the home screen, very
similar to Spotify: we've got playlists
made for us, the weekly
recommendation, mixes, what we've listened to
recently. Further down we can see
friend activity, since it works
as a social network with
other users. Here, in notifications, we can also
see what has come in recently.
In the search area we can see
recommended artists that can find us,
or playlists based on what we
listen to. We've got the genres: this
is all rock.
Create is aimed more at content
creators. And the search
engine, let's see. Let's search for Queen — see how fast
we find it: it tells us that's the best
match, and here we have the band's
profile, where we can see songs or info,
their photo
carousel. Further down are their social
networks. And here we can
also see their discography.
We can see where they appear, which
collections they're in, and similar artists.
Now let's actually try a song: we'll
play their second track and we'll hear
how it sounds.
We move to the next song, and we see
that you can skip forward too.